marcosorder.com 2018-09-07

# Marcos Pizza |

   | 

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. 

**First Party Cookie Integration:**  
We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.marcosorder.com//adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61919&cname=Marcos%20Pizza&cmagic=373bf4&clogo=61919.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

**Third Party Cookie Integration:**  
We may use third party companies to provide advertising services and/or to collect certain information when you visit and interact with our website. These third-party companies may collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website [and/or other websites] in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These third-party companies may use cookies and other technologies to recognize your browser to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. You may visit the Network Advertising Initiative, www.networkadvertising.org/choices or the Digital Advertising Alliance, http://www.aboutads.info/, to learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests on your browser, from their respective members and participants. 

With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook. 

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. 

To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent on your first use of the service. You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, email, address or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information. We may keep data indefinitely. 

We may share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with trusted partners associated with Marco's Pizza Franchising in order to provide you with relevant advertising, offers or services. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies or are a California residents legally entitled (at no charge and no more than once annually) to request information about how we may have shared your information with others for direct marketing purposes. Contact us at: 

websupport@pyrimont.com or  
Privacy Policy Request  
Pyrimont Operating Solutions  
6320 Rucker Road, Suite F  
Indianapolis, IN 46220  

Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device and your identity. Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. 

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so. 

This privacy policy was last updated on September 19th, 2017. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
